<Publish>
	<ModId Value="79186" />
	<DisplayName Value="Simple Mod Checker Plus" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Mod load notification, backup/restore game/mods settings/keybinds, and more tools." />
	<LongDescription>I'm a simple man; I see "Loaded {x} mods", I start playing.

This mod adds a **persistent** notification to the Main Menu, showing how many mods have loaded in the current session.

The notification will automatically hide once a Game or Editor is loaded.

If for some reason a broken mod prevents other mods from loading, just by looking at the number you can recognize something is wrong.

If you don't see the notification at all, it means no mods were loaded and you need to restart the game.

## Additional features
* Get notified when a Setting file is corrupted.
* See list of all mods loaded in the current session (grouped by Code Mods and non-Code/packaged mods).
* Backup and Restore Game Settings and selected Mod Settings, and all keybinds (game and mod).
* Automatically restore settings with values saved to 'Profile 1' on startup.
* Trigger a mod verification checkup for all/selected downloaded mods (checks weather the files has been tampered, or if there's more than one version of the same mode is on storage). Found on the "" list, which when clicked will launch a set of checks to ensure the integrity of the mods. It will check if you have multiple version of the same mod downloaded and also the integrity of each file in your whole PDX Mods folder. Any files ending with "backup" are ignored. The process will only inform you about the verification result, any other steps to resolve those issues will need to be done manually.
* Remove the "Resume" button in the launcher and/or the "Continue Game" button in the main menu.
* `ModsData/ModDatabase.json` is now only used for enabling/disabling what mod to back up. If a mod is causing issue, you can manually edit the `ModDatabase.json` file until I get an update out.
* [REMOVED] ~~Get notified when .Prefab or .cok files have missing CIDs. (Includes automatic backup, original idea by Konsi/Mimonsi)~~ (Removed as backup CIDs are no longer necessary).
* [REMOVED] ~~Get notified when any of your locally installed or published mods includes vanilla DLLs.~~ (Removed as its part of the base game since 1.2.0f1).

**IMPORTANT**: It is required to make separate backup manually in Profile 1 for Game Settings, Mod Settings and Keybinds first time for the Auto Restore to work afterwards.

### By default on exit, the corrupted setting files will be deleted automatically.

# All options are optional...

Check Options in-game for the current list of supported mods for settings backup/restore.

Safe to remove anytime.

Find me on **Cities: Skylines** Official Discord or **Cities: Skylines Modding** Discord.

Feedback / Bug Report: https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1287440491239047208
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot01.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot02.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot03.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot04.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot05.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot06.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="3.4.5" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.5" />
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<ChangeLog>
- NEW: Option to remove the "Resume" button in the launcher.
- NEW: Option to disable the "Continue Game" button in the main menu.
- Removed deprecated CID backup options that wasn't removed 3.4.4.
	</ChangeLog>
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/qstar-inc/cities2-SimpleModChecker" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/U2PSjUzUuF" />
	<ExternalLink Type="buymeacoffee" Url="https://buymeacoffee.com/starq" />
</Publish>
